<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fund 9 on</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/</link><description>Recent content in Fund 9 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>500+ ₳Community Sent to Conferences</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/500pluscommunitysenttoconferences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/500pluscommunitysenttoconferences/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - 500+ ₳Community Sent to Conferences # As a new Cardano dApp with a lot of hustle &amp;amp; desire to grow quickly, we lack go-to-market resources to send this community to conferences and 100x user adoption &amp;amp; revenue in the next couple of months. Exhibit at major industry conferences with free tickets for the Cardano community to share the Cardano gospel, meet each other in person, and sell to decision-makers to 100x user adoption and revenue.</description></item><item><title>Adacheems: Optimize the value of NFT</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/adacheems-optimizevalueofnft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/adacheems-optimizevalueofnft/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Adacheems: Optimize the value of NFT # Ideascale Proposer: Adacheems Requested Budget: 50000 The other NFTs on the Market are too wasteful to just be on display. We bring an NFT world that includes economy, real-world connectivity, and stronger interactions for owners. AdaCheems NFT Project - Optimizing Use Values and Building the Economy of the NFT. We bring an NFT world that includes economy, real-world connectivity, and stronger interactions for owners.</description></item><item><title>BEST WAY TO ATTRACT REAL GAMERS</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/bestwaytoattractrealgamers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/bestwaytoattractrealgamers/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - BEST WAY TO ATTRACT REAL GAMERS # Ideascale Proposer: Miverse Multiverse Requested Budget: 54810 The best praise for the team is your vote, please leave a comment if you are interested!!!
Not just real gamers hate on-chained games, but we also have no sustainable, long-term way to attract - educate - convince them to try our good games. Miverse provides a comic platform and produces a comic - one of the ultimate weapons to attract real gamers on-chained.</description></item><item><title>Blockchain Educational dApp</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/blockchainedudapps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/blockchainedudapps/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Blockchain Educational dApp # Support the Ghana team with their educational proposal This proposal seeks to develop an educational dapp on blockchain and its yields as a safe, long-term investment for the youth in Ghana. Users boarded onto the platform through community outreach, mainly across the various Ghanaian universities and beyond, will have a variety of topics to choose from, with compact yet interactive lessons to complete at their own pace</description></item><item><title>Cardano ERP - Grow Africa</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-growafrica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-growafrica/</guid><description> Catalyst TV - Cardano ERP - Grow Africa # Cardano needs more developers from Africa to participate in Emurgo Academy training and developing enterprise-grade products on the Cardano blockchain. Cardano needs more developers from Africa to participate in Emurgo Academy training and developing enterprise-grade products on the Cardano blockchain.
Ideascale Proposer: Cardano ERP Requested Budget: 23700 Tracking links: # https://cerp.dev https://vimeo.com/695045590/f388d90666</description></item><item><title>Cardano ERP - Grow Asia</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-growasia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-growasia/</guid><description> Catalyst TV - Cardano ERP - Grow Asia # Cardano needs more developers from Asia to participate in Emurgo Academy training and develop enterprise-grade products on the Cardano blockchain. The requested funds will be used to cover Emurgo Academy training fees for experienced developers residing within Asia.
Ideascale Proposer: Cardano ERP Requested Budget: 47400 Tracking links: # https://vimeo.com/695045590/f388d90666 https://cerp.dev</description></item><item><title>Cardano ERP - Main Project</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-mainproject/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-mainproject/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano ERP - Main Project # There is no intelligent, open-source, Cardano-native ERP system to provide for seamless integration of, and optimized standard user experience for, business, enterprise, and government-focused dApps. Cardano ERP will provide for seamless integration of, and optimized user experience for, business, enterprise, and government focused dApps via an open-source, standardized modular solution.
Ideascale Proposer: Cardano ERP Requested Budget: 491400 Support the team by voting for this proposal, leave a comment for the proposer if any doubt cross your mind!</description></item><item><title>Cardano ERP for Catalyst</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-forcatalyst/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoerp-forcatalyst/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano ERP for Catalyst # There is currently no intelligent, open-source Cardano-native accounting/auditing system. CERP for Catalyst will be an intelligent open-source Cardano-native accounting/auditing system consisting of a GL, COTI Pay integration, funds/revenue receipts modules, and financial + audit reports.
Ideascale Proposer: Cardano ERP Requested Budget: 100000 Support the team by voting for this proposal, leave a comment for the proposer if any doubt cross your mind!</description></item><item><title>Cardano Forest - blocktree.asia</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoforest/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/cardanoforest/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano Forest - blocktree.asia # We established a team to work with tree planting organizations in Vietnam to introduce the blockchain technologies to solve their problem in providing transparency, auditability and measurelity to their donors.
We have worked with Gaia Nature Conservation to support us on planting the trees. Gaia is a national not-for-profit organization of Vietnam. Gaia empowers people and applies its experience to stop biodiversity degradation with the aim of creating a future where humans live in harmony with our rich and beautiful nature.</description></item><item><title>CH2O Africa - ADA NFT Charity</title><link>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/ch20africa-ada-nft-charity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jennyberry.github.io/new-eth/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/ch20africa-ada-nft-charity/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - CH2O Africa- ADA NFT Charity # Charities are not transparent 💸, limited in resources, and wells aren&amp;rsquo;t maintained builds a non-profit that digs wells and creates NFTs. Hardware oracles in the wells transmit a token to these NFT holders. Donors/Holders get instant validation of their contributions.
Ideascale Proposer: Dan Rodman Requested Budget: 509395 Stop by and Kudo to this proposal which wants to help provide clean drinking water in Africa 💧.</description></item></channel></rss>